A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 3 FA1554
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1952, 1972-1973, 1980-2012; 2; 18.27 Cubic Feet 38 legal document boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Establishment of a Stroke Center, 00-730, 2000-2008 (Box 40, Folder 386)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Implementation of Comprehensive School-Based Smoking Control Program in School Children and Medical College Students of China, 00-729, 2000-2008 (Box 41, Folder 387)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Megsin Gene, 05-827, 2004-2007, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 388)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), A Pilot Program for a Comprehensive System of Nursing Education, 98-692, 1999-2009 (Box 41, Folder 389-392)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Reform of Medical Education, 03-780, 2003-2007 (Box 41, Folder 393)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Reform of Medical Education, 03-780, CMB, 2004 October 19 (Box 41, Folder 393)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), 5-Year Students' Investigation Projects at Existing Rural Practice Sites, 05-825, 2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 394)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), Clinical Practice Base, Phase II, 01-753, 2001, 2003-2007 (Box 42, Folder 395)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), Comprehensive Five-Year Medical Education Program, 02-763, 2001-2008 (Box 42, Folder 396)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), Library Enrichment Project, 05-824, 2005, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 397)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), Textbook on High Altitude Sickness, 01-760, 2000-2001, 2003-2006 (Box 42, Folder 398)
  - Ulaan Baatar Nursing School Medical College, Educational Improvement, 01-754, 1993, 2001-2002, 2004-2005, 2007, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 399)
  - Ulaan Baatar Nursing School Medical College, Nursing Education, 93-598, 1993-2002, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 400)
  - University of Medicine 2 (Institute of Medicine 2), Development of Post-Graduate Diploma Course in Medical Education, 02-765, 2001-2008 (Box 42, Folder 401)
  - University of Medicine 2 (Institute of Medicine 2), Reform of Medical Ethics Teaching, 03-789, 2003-2008 (Box 42, Folder 402)
  - University of Medicine 2 (Institute of Medicine 2), Repair of Damaged Buildings of UM2, Due to Cyclone Nargis, 08-914, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 403)
  - University of Medicine 2 (Institute of Medicine 2), Staff Development, 02-775, 2002-2007 (Box 42, Folder 404)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Allied Health Education, 96-659, 1996-20007 (Box 42, Folder 405)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Allied Health Education, 96-659, 1996-2007 (Box 43, Folder 406)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Anti-Microbial Resistance, 96-681, 1999-2008 (Box 43, Folder 407)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), A Center for Medical Education, Research and Development, 00-721, 1999-2009 (Box 43, Folder 408-409)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Chinese Birth Defects Bank, 03-783, 2001-2007 (Box 43, Folder 410)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Clinical Laboratory Accreditation, 00-737, 2000-2007 (Box 43, Folder 411)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Clinical Skills Education, 96-649, 1995-2007 (Box 44, Folder 412)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Evidence Based Medicine, 98-680, 1998-2007 (Box 44, Folder 413-414)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), New Program on Medical Education, 96-660, 1996-2007 (Box 44, Folder 415)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Problem Solving for Better Health, 95-623, 1995-2007 (Box 44, Folder 416-417)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Reform the Human Resource Management (HRM) System to a Build a High Performance Team for the 21st Century, 00-722, 2000-2009 (Box 45, Folder 418)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Tele-Medicine Project, 98-679, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 419)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, International Workshop on the Future Direction of the Nursing Profession in China, 06-846, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 420)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, A New Model for the Improvement in Pregnant Outcomes in Tibet, 02-778, 2001-2003, 2006-207 (Box 45, Folder 421)
- Contingent Fund, 1989-1993, 1995-2006; 3; 2.35 Cubic Feet 5 legal document boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Most the of the documents in this series primarily pertain to the financial commitment and reimbursement for the CMB grantees. These commitments include travel and hotel stipends, grant checks, and other activities.
  - Ade, Wolfgang R., 98-685, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 422)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Cancer Research, Beijing Medical University, 81-397, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 423)
  - American Public Health Association, 00-733, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 424)
  - American Public Health Association, Liu Xiu, 00-733, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 425)
  - Art Work, China School, 96-650, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 426)
  - Association of American Medicla Colleges, Academic Medicine Journal, 98-685, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 427)
  - Beasley, R. Palmer, China Consultant, 92-579, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 428)
  - Beijing Medical University, CMB Awards, Ethics Conference, 96-650, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 429)
  - Beijing Medical University, Medical Exchanges, China-USA, 99-705, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 430)
  - Beijing Medical University, Medical Writing and Edition Consultation, 92-580, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 431)
  - Beijing Medical University, Sun Jiangping, Peiking Union Medical College (PUMC) History, 98-685, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 432)
  - Beijing Medical University, Translation of Medical Ethic Textbook, 1996, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 433)
  - Beijing Medical University, Translation of Medical Ethic Textbook, 1996, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 434)
  - Benjamin, Denis R., Review of West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS) Project, 99-705, 1999, 2001, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 435)
  - Bridge to China Foundation, Juijiang Medical College, 81-397, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 436)
  - Buchanan, J. Robert, China Trip, 2000 January, 99-705, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 437)
  - Carrico, C. James, Trauma Center Proposal, 01-741 (Box 46, Folder 438)
  - Central South University, Xiang-Ya School of Medicine, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 439)
  - Chavigy, Kathrine, Rural Practice in China, 98-685, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 440)
  - Chiangmai University, Faculty of Nursing, Publication of Nursing Speeches, 02-779, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 441)
  - Chiangmai University, Faculty of Nursing, Visit Medical and Nursing Education Centers, 01-750, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 442)
  - China Medical Board, Medical Ethics Meeting, 1998 May 1, 96-650, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 443)
  - China Medical Board, Medical Ethics Meeting, 1998 May 1, 96-650, Minutes, Meeting, International Medical Education, Ad Hoc Adv Steering Committee, 1998 March 20-21 (Box 46, Folder 443)
  - China Medical University, Suyan Tong, 92-580, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 444)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, History, 00-733, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 445)
  - Clinical Assessment, China, Paula Stillman, 81-397, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 446)
  - Clinical Skills, Zheng Shu, Zhejiang Medical University, 81-397, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 447)
  - Columbia University, Tse Den, 00-733, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 448)
  - Dale, David C., 99-705, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 449)
  - Dohner, Charles W., Consultant, Medical Globlization Workshop, 96-50, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 450)
  - Dohner, Charles W., 02-779, 04-802, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 451)
  - University of Dundee, Ivinurs Meeting, 02-779, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 452)
  - 1st World Medicine Summit, 2005 June 27-29 (Box 46, Folder 453)
  - Educational Review, China, 2000 September 25-October 10, 99-705 (Box 46, Folder 454)
  - Halloran, Edward J., Planning Grant, Hospital in China Grant, 04-802, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 455)
  - Harbin Medical University, Planning Grant for Medical Reform, 99-705, 1999-2001 (Box 46, Folder 456)
  - Harbin Medical University, Policy Training Program, 02-779, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 457)
  - Hanoi Medical University, 100th Anniversary Gift, 02-779, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 458)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health, School History, 01-750, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 459)
  - Hasting Center, Publication, Ethics Conference at Beijing Medical University, 1999, 00-733, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 460)
  - Higgins, Robert, 99-705, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 461)
  - Honoraria, Review China Grant Proposals, 81-397, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 462)
  - Hotez, Peter, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Parasitology Consultant, 96-650, 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 463)
  - Hu, Jing, Translations, 96-650, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 464)
  - Human Subjects Planning Meeting, 2001 March 6-7, 00-733, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 465)
  - University of Indonesia, H. M. K. Tadjudin, 92-580, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 466)
  - Jaffe, Kenneth, 00-7433, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 467)
  - Jiogliang, Zhou, School of Public Health, Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), 1989 (Box 47, Folder 468)
  - Jiujiang University, Book on Rural Medical Education Reform, 04-802, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 469)
  - Lazuras, Gerald, Travel to Guilin, etc., 99-705, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 470)
  - Lazuras, Gerald, Assess for China Schools, 01-741, 2001-2003 (Box 47, Folder 471)
  - Lehman, John, Hanoi Medical University (HMU)/Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS) China Grants, 96-650, 98-685, 1996-1999 (Box 47, Folder 472)
  - Lemire, Ronald J., Beijing Medical University (BMU), 99-705, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 473)
  - MacLeod, Gordon, 99-705, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 474)
  - Mayuex, Richard, 99-705, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 478)
  - Medical Education Review, Evaluation Forms, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 479-480)
  - Medical Education Review, Evaluation Forms, Educational Review (Box 47, Folder 479)
  - Myers, Wayne, 01-741, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 481)
  - National University of Laos, History, 01-741, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 482)
  - Newan, Frank, Wayne Myers, Consultants, 02-779, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 483)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Mei Wun Li, Legacy Health System, 00-733, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 484)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Visit to United States of America, Rural Health, 04-802, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 485)
  - Panamerican Federation, Conference Bogata, 1999 July 21-23, 99-705 (Box 47, Folder 486)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 85th Anniversary, 2002 October 20 (Box 47, Folder 487)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Computer Equipment, Lui Huaping, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 488)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Ba Denisan, China Medical Board Board Meeting, 1998 December, 98-685 (Box 47, Folder 489)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Ba Denisan, 01-741, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 490)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Expenses, President's Meeting, 2006 June, 06-833 (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Freezers for Genetics Groups, Kumming, 01-740, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 492)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Gu Xin and Ma Jingyun Visit to the China Medical Board Office, 1999 October, 99-705 (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Ma Jingyun, 01-750, 06-833, 2002, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 494)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Medical Surgical Nursing Program, 92-580, 1995, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 495)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Medical Teaching Reform in 21st Century, 99-705, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 496)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Office of International Exchange, Computer, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 497)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Publication of History of PUMC Teaching, 96-650, 99-705, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 498)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Research!America, Memebership, 01-741, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 499)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Supreme Forum on Medical Education, Shanghai, 2003 November, 02-779 (Box 48, Frame 500)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Translation of Chinese Scroll, 98-685, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 501)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Jie Ping wu and Jie Fu Huang, Visit to the China Medical Board Office, 1998 June, 96-650 (Box 48, Folder 502)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), She Yun, PUMC History Translation, 96-650, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 503)
  - Peking University Health Science Center (PUHSC), 90th Anniversary, 2002 October 26 (Box 48, Folder 504)
  - Peking University Health Science Center (PUHSC), Association of Medical Education for the Western Pacific Region (AMEWPR), 2006 April-May, 04-802, 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 505)
  - Peking University Health Science Center (PUHSC), Planning for Family Medicine Conference, 02-779, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 506)
  - President's Meeting, Herbert Pardes, 1998 September, 96-650 (Box 48, Folder 507)
  - Rosenblatt, Roger, 99-705, 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 508)
  - Saver, Barry, Zhejiang Medical University (ZMU) Family Medicine, 96-650, 98-696, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 509)
  - Scientific Reviews, 01-741, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 510)
  - Seminar U.S. Biomedicine Research, Beijing, 2002 September 23-24, 01-750, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 511)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Consultant, Kenneth Jaffe, Rehabilitation Medicine, 96-650, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 512)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Feasibility Study/Telemedicine in Rural China, 96-650, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 513)
  - Sichuan University, Study of Higher Education in the USA, 01-741, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 514)
  - Siegler, Mark, Expenses, Human Trial Conference, 2001 January, 01-750 (Box 48, Folder 515)
  - Strand, Donn, 00-733, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 516)
  - Sugarman, Jonathan, Family Medicine, Hanoi Medical College, 00-733, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 517)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Chen Shou Bin, 81-397, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 518)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Zhou Jiongliang, Meeting, 1991 November-December, 81-397, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 519)
  - University of Texas, Medical Center at Houston, Jay Glasser, 02-779, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 520)
  - University of Texas, Houston, Planning for Medicine-Public Health Conference, 02-779, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 521)
  - University of Texas, Sichuan Delegation Visit, 2006 March 24, 04-802 (Box 48, Folder 522)
  - Tibet Medical College (TMC), 100th Anniversary Gift, 01-750, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 523)
  - Tibet Medical College (TMC), Kahn Min Training Program Supplement, 01-741, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 524)
  - Tibet Medical College (TMC), Ouzhu Luobu, English Language Translation, 04-802, 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 525)
  - Tibet Medical College (TMC), Visit to the US, 2002 March, 01-750, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 526)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), 30th Anniversary & Symposium, 01-751, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 527)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), English Language Program, 04-802, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 528)
  - Tibet University Medical College (TUMC), English Language Program, 04-802, Tiibet Project-Interviews, 2005 March (Box 49, Folder 528)
  - Translation of Shanghai Medical University (SMU) History, 99-705, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 529)
  - Tribhuvan University, Gifts, 01-750, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 530)
  - University of Washington, Dinner for Central South University Group, 04-802, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 531)
  - University of Washington, Rehabilitation Medicine Project, 01-750, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 532)
  - University of Washington, Sichuan Delegation, 01-741, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 533)
  - WebMD Professional Publishing Books for China Medical Board Grantees Institutions, 04-802, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 534)
  - Weisbuch, Jonathan, 96-650, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 535)
  - Wentz, Anne Coleton, Nepal Review, 92--580, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 536)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), 90th Anniversary Gift, 99-705, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 537)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Benjamin Seltzer, 92-580, 1995-1997 (Box 49, Folder 538)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), History of West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), 99-705, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 539)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Medical Education Conference, 2002 May, 01-750 (Box 49, Folder 540)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Planning, Laboratory Accreditation, 98-686, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 541)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Zhang Zhaoda, Mao Meng, China Medical Board (CMB) Board Meeting, 1999 June 7, 96-650, 99-705, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Win, Myo, 01-741, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 543)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, Ren Huimin, 00-730, 1998-2000 (Box 49, Folder 544)
  - Cai, Xiaodong, Translation of Wu Jie Ping Book, 01-741, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 545)
  - Yanxin, Han, 92-580 (Box 49, Folder 546)
  - Yao, Tai, 99-705, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 547)
  - Yao, Tai, 00-733, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Zhe, Dong and Wang Debing, China Medical Board (CMB), Board Meeting, 1999 December, 99-705 (Box 49, Folder 549)
  - Zhe, Dong, USA Visit, 2000 October, 00-733 (Box 49, Folder 550)
  - Zhejiang University School of Medicine, Zusom History, 00-733, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 551)